[id: lnkqsaqi]
[ar:Queen]
[ti:We Will Rock You]
[al:Greatest Hits I II & III Platinum Collection]
[00:00.00]Artist: Queen
[00:00.00]Title: We Will Rock You
[00:00.00]Album: Greatest Hits I II & III Platinum Collection
[00:00.00][00:23.55][00:33.99][00:47.08][00:57.43][01:04.46][01:10.54][01:34.89]
[00:12.66]Buddy you’re a boy make a big noise
[00:14.47]Playin’ in the street gonna be a big man some day
[00:17.52]You got mud on yo’ face
[00:19.46][00:42.95][01:06.39]You big disgrace
[00:20.96]Kickin’ your can all over the place
[00:23.75][00:52.37][01:15.30]Singin'
[00:24.71][00:29.84][00:47.48][00:53.32][01:10.99][01:16.73][01:28.46]We will we will rock you
[00:36.17]Buddy you’re a young man hard man
[00:38.00]Shoutin’ in the street gonna take on the world some day
[00:41.21]You got blood on yo’ face
[00:44.43]Wavin’ your banner all over the place
[00:59.71]Buddy you’re an old man poor man
[01:01.54]Pleadin’ with your eyes gonna make you some peace some day
[01:04.82]You got mud on your face
[01:07.81]Somebody better put you back in your place
[01:22.54]Everybody, We will we will rock you
[01:34.18]Alright!
