[id: owovwvsh]
[ar:Megadeth]
[ti:Sudden Death]
[al:Guitar Hero: Warriors of Rock]
[00:01.77]Artist: MEGADETH
[00:05.34]Album: Guitar Hero: Warriors of Rock
[00:11.47]Title: Sudden Death
[00:16.41]By: (c)2010 by MadMaxx---NYC---
[00:27.41][01:36.41][02:06.71][04:59.36]
[01:06.93]His evil highness born from disaster,
[01:09.82]To dominate and kill.
[01:16.21]But Listening, murder machine.
[01:18.88]Falls majesty, standing perfectly still.
[01:25.14]And It’s raining, raining down evil.
[01:28.46]What a mountain of Black Ice
[01:31.71]Like a good old fashioned beating within,
[01:34.27]Isn’t that your life?
[01:36.73][04:32.02]All alone
[01:37.66][04:33.04]And left abandoned
[01:38.86][04:34.61]With a sentence,
[01:40.44][04:36.05]You’ve been handed.
[01:41.96][04:37.67]All your Angels will ignore you,
[01:44.85][04:40.48]As your life flashes before you.
[01:47.99][04:43.61]Even still, you keep on fighting,
[01:51.05][04:46.50]Through the thunder and the lightning.
[01:54.13][04:49.64]And our heavy senses flow,
[02:01.57]Your sudden death from above!
[02:09.39]Was Frozen like a prisoner to break
[02:12.52]First Tied Us Up, leather spears.
[02:18.74]Sits and waits beneath the depths of hell
[02:21.68]The creeping men nothing but despair.
[02:27.80]The beast is just genetically programmed,
[02:30.76]Time to destroy time to go bezerk.
[02:34.07]To see the end of our war,
[02:36.73]To see the end of the earth!
[02:40.16]---(Guitar /Drum Fills)---
[02:55.45]Stopping at nothing, Punchdrunk,
[02:57.45]From the blood that he’s tasted.
[03:01.07]Tearing your soul apart,
[03:03.32]Not one bit of your pain will be wasted.
[03:07.35]Now death descends upon you,
[03:10.10]Like a bloody white dove.
[03:13.32]Bringin your retribution,
[03:15.71]A sudden death from above!
[03:18.87]---(Guitar Solo)---(D. Mustaine)
[04:57.07]Your sudden death from above!!
