[id: owqallss]
[ar:Deathstars]
[ti:Syndrome]

[00:15.92]Such a dirty disease fights under your skin

[00:21.87]It eats and it burns and it rapes and it turns

[00:26.81]Such an infested thing laying eggs within

[00:31.98]They hatch in your lunges with dirty tounges


[00:44.63][01:42.02][02:29.39][02:49.96]I'm gonna touch you inside

[00:49.82][01:47.27][02:34.15][02:55.16]I'm gonna be your little child

[00:55.13][01:52.47][02:39.34][03:00.31]Right where your blood runs wild

[00:59.72][01:57.01]Inside - that's where I'll hide


[01:13.70]Such a violent syndrome tapped to your spine

[01:19.00]It's a virus storm and it's about to be born


[01:24.15]Such a violent word that wants to be heard

[01:29.29]You got me deep within and under your skin











[02:44.05][03:04.45]Inside

