[ar: Deathstars]
[ti: Metal]
[al: The Greatest Hits On The Earth]
[Encoding: utf-8]
[length: 03:50]
[id: hahlzqsk]
[00:00.00]Artist: Deathstars
[00:03.15]Album: The Greatest Hits On The Earth
[00:06.59]Title: Metal
[00:09.14]By: Walter
[00:13.83]
[00:21.31]
[00:29.58]The voice of bleeding from the desperate cuts
[00:32.82]is been flooding for days
[00:36.11]The heart is fighting to a sickeless breath
[00:39.23]you annoy love ... ???
[00:41.78]
[00:42.34]Metal, metal
[00:50.30]
[00:55.71]The blade is thirsty for the cheese of mankind
[00:59.01]is been tricking for days
[01:02.32]She´s a swan ??? beside of god
[01:05.61]the blood thirsty as she is
[01:07.96]
[01:10.82]I want to spit it out - tap - tap - tap - crash - doom
[01:17.16]The shots are ringing out - tap - tap - tap - crash - boom
[01:21.71]
[01:22.01]Metal, metal
[01:29.80]
[01:35.46]The lamps are slipping on theme of black flames
[01:38.57]the clock help for the wars
[01:41.68]Your tasted flesh is the clashes of doom
[01:45.04].. purse and shores ???
[01:47.41]
[01:50.33]I want to spit it out - tap - tap - tap - crash - doom
[01:56.73]The shots are ringing out - tap - tap - tap - crash - boom
[02:01.28]
[02:04.58]I will the west turn to east will feast
[02:10.86]Do it for beauty in the pleasures of the beast
[02:15.02]
[02:27.91]Teach, dirt, slaves, true, bring me power
[02:34.37]I´m gonna teach you by dark, 
[02:36.24]I´m gonna teach you by night
[02:37.74]I´m just receiving the word from the ... of destruction ???
[02:41.09]
[02:41.41]Teach, dirt, slaves, true, bring me power
[02:47.31]I´m gonna teach you by dark, I´m gonna teach you by night
[02:50.93]The perfect slave will kiss two white lips of the night
[02:54.28]
[02:55.90]I´m gonna kiss the night
[02:57.77]
[02:59.01]I want to spit it out - tap - tap - tap - crash - doom
[03:05.36]The shots are ringing out - tap - tap - tap - crash - boom
[03:10.04]
[03:10.77]Metal
[03:12.21]I want to spit it out - tap - tap - tap - crash - doom
[03:16.57]Metal
[03:18.56]The shots are ringing out - tap - tap - tap - crash - boom
[03:23.03]
[03:26.69]I will the west turn to east will feast
[03:32.90]Do it for beauty in the pleasures of the beast
[03:37.75]

