[id: qlcwnksq]
[ar:Delain]
[ti:April Rain]
[al:April Rain]
[by:DW]
[00:02.43].: Delain :.
[00:12.72].: April  Rain :.
[00:19.65].: Album Version:.
[00:25.14].: By:DW :.
[00:39.76][01:18.00][01:45.11][02:11.00][02:37.75][03:30.20][03:55.42]
[00:52.16]How does it feel when all you’re counting on is scatterbrained
[00:59.34]Every wind that you have sailed upon, a hurricane
[01:05.70]Every summer you have seen was filled with april rain
[01:13.82][02:06.27]It doesn’t get easy, don’t you know
[01:18.68][01:31.78][02:11.22][02:24.39][03:56.26][04:09.43]Fortune smiles on you
[01:24.36]You’re not watching, dig that hole deeper
[01:37.65][02:30.07][04:15.11]You’re not watching, create your own fate
[01:45.14]Count your blessings and prepare to change your point of view
[01:51.66]All those days that you spend waiting won’t come back to you
[01:58.72]Take off the glasses that have treated your world black and grey
[02:16.78]You’re not watching, deeper oh deeper
[03:03.50]Keep raining 3x
[03:16.86][03:30.58]Keep raining, 'cause we are blind,
[03:20.44]Keep raining, ‘cause we are tired,
[03:23.81]Keep raining, 'cause we are blind to fortune’s guidance now
[03:33.64][03:48.69]It will keep raining, ‘cause we are tired,
[03:42.75]It keeps raining, ‘cause we are blind oh,
[04:01.81]You’re not watching,  deeper oh deeper
