[id: osiosoqp]
[ar:Die Happy]
[ti:Whatever]
[al:No Nuts No Glory]
[00:20.35]I can barely see your face today
[00:24.67]Behind your hands
[00:26.67]You say there's no time to waste
[00:31.42]Hoping that miracles are up to date
[00:39.18][01:55.16]Before you reach the end
[00:43.74]You say:
[00:45.99]How could a „Lucky Jinx“ like you
[00:47.62]Believe in a happy end
[00:52.18]You must have known you will lose again
[00:56.43]Still hoping tomorrow is a better day
[01:03.79]Your tears run down your face

[01:08.16][02:00.16][02:49.60][03:28.72][Refrain]
[01:09.29][02:00.60][03:09.54][03:29.16]Whatever makes you strong again
[01:12.60][02:03.72][03:12.60][03:31.72]Whatever makes you proud
[01:15.79][02:06.91][03:15.72][03:34.85]Whatver makes you whole again
[01:18.97][02:10.10][03:19.04][03:38.04]Please keep it on your mind
[01:22.10][02:13.35][03:21.99][03:41.10]That I'll always run to you
[01:25.10][02:16.29][03:25.22][03:44.16]Give you everything I have
[01:29.54][03:48.86]I'll do anything, anything, anything

[01:36.79]I can barely hear your voice today
[01:41.47]Your words are gone
[01:43.54]I will try to bring them back to you
[01:47.91]Hoping
[01:49.97]They bring you miracles that you prayed for

[02:20.54]I'll do anything, anything, anything for you

[02:30.60]I will cheer you up somehow
[02:33.54]I will nail your lips to a smile
[02:37.04]I'll be your clown
[02:40.35]Let you scream into my face
[02:42.97]For all the sinners, all the shame
[02:47.97]And for you


