[id: ihakcnqw]
[ar:Die Happy]
[ti:Violent Dreams]
[al:Supersonic Speed]
[00:19.56]Sun is getting down
[00:21.62]Shadows get bigger
[00:24.23]Mean noises around
[00:26.48]The air tastes bitter

[00:29.37]Pictures start to move
[00:31.42]They make bad faces
[00:34.09]Bats are flying ‘round
[00:36.34]In fast races

[00:39.12]The moon is greeting me
[00:41.52]But I can’t see it
[00:43.65]The bad spell is here
[00:46.30]And I sure can feel it

[00:48.79]Creatures ‘round my bed
[00:51.45]I can hear them mumble
[00:53.73]Their eyes shine red
[00:56.34]And they stumble

[00:58.71][01:01.23][02:12.81][02:15.23]I don’t wanna die

[01:03.48][02:17.78][02:57.44][03:18.66][03:25.00]Scare me every night
[01:05.55][02:19.75][02:59.33][03:20.47]Against you I will fight
[01:08.23][02:22.43][03:02.09][03:22.94]‘till the sun will rise
[01:10.15][02:24.22][03:03.89]I’m living this hell
[01:12.40][01:22.24][02:26.60][02:36.67][03:06.22][03:16.07][03:17.50]Violent dreams

[01:13.79][02:28.04][03:07.83][03:27.33]And when it’s light
[01:15.74][02:29.87][03:09.52][03:29.25]The daemons taking flight
[01:18.29][02:31.96][03:11.96][03:31.44]Out of mind and sight
[01:20.20][02:34.06][03:13.81][03:33.72]I’m rid of this spell
[01:26.96]
[01:33.60]Sun is rising up
[01:35.66]Shadows get thinner
[01:38.10]After last night
[01:39.92]I am the winner

[01:42.79]This night isn’t better
[01:45.62]I don’t wanna stay here
[01:47.87]Why should it matter
[01:50.15]My visions are queer

[01:52.65]Cold sweat on my skin
[01:55.09]My heart is beating
[01:57.71]Might have been a sin
[01:59.99]‘Cause my hands are bleeding

[02:02.93]It’s been already years
[02:05.58]Since it first happened
[02:07.79]All I have are tears
[02:10.06]And no weapon




[02:40.72]Go away bad ghost, disappear
[02:44.54]You don’t make me feel any fear
[02:49.72]I do not give a damn ‘bout you
[02:53.39]What did I do to you?




[03:35.94]Violent dreams…
