[id: clpzhzqp]
[ar:Disturbed]
[ti:Stupify]
[al:The Sickness]
[by:Despair]

[00:09.63]Yeah, bringing you another disturbing creation
[00:12.17]from the mind of one sick animal who can't tell the difference
[00:15.52]and gets stupified
[00:16.15][00:39.35][00:49.07][01:08.19][01:18.50][01:47.50][01:57.30][02:16.32][02:27.18][02:46.50][03:12.82][03:23.10][03:44.00][03:54.00][04:04.00]
[00:19.33]I've been waiting my whole life for just one fuck
[00:22.31]And all I needed was just one fuck
[00:24.81]How can you say that you don't give a fuck
[00:27.30][00:37.07][01:35.71][01:45.55]I find myself stupified, coming back again
[00:29.72]All I wanted was just one fuck
[00:32.15]One tiny little innocent fuck
[00:34.60]And when I feel like I'm shit out of luck
[00:39.36][00:49.08][01:47.80][01:57.50]why, do you like playing around with
[00:41.97][00:51.88][01:50.50][01:59.93]My, narrow scope of reality
[00:44.54][01:52.89]I, can feel it all start slipping
[00:46.85][01:55.04]I think I'm breaking down
[00:54.19][02:02.70]I, can feel it all start slipping away
[00:57.65][02:05.99]See but I don't get it
[00:59.41][01:09.58][02:07.59][02:17.51][03:16.00]Don't you think maybe we could put it on credit
[01:01.87][01:11.69][02:10.16][02:19.92][03:18.50]Don't you think it can take control when I don't let it
[01:04.40][01:14.18][01:16.75][02:12.99][02:22.54][02:25.00][03:21.33]I get stupified
[01:06.12][02:14.45]It's all the same you say
[01:07.44][02:15.83]Live with it
[01:08.20][02:16.52][03:14.82]But I don't get it
[01:28.55]All the people in the left wing rock
[01:31.06]And all the people in the right wing rock
[01:33.33]And all the people in the underground rock
[01:38.13]All the people in the high rise rock
[01:40.67]And all the people in the projects rock
[01:43.10]And all la gente en the barrio rock
[02:28.34][02:38.06](Mefached)
[02:54.67]And don't deny me
[02:57.98]No baby now, don't deny me
[03:02.63]And darlin' don't be afraid
[03:25.50][03:30.32][03:35.25][03:40.12]Look in my face, stare in my soul
[03:27.10][03:32.10][03:37.15][03:41.90][04:01.00]I begin to stupify, Rah!
[03:44.50][03:47.00][03:49.50][03:52.00]Look in my face, step in my soul
[03:54.50][03:57.00][03:59.27]Look in my face, steppin´ in my soul
