[id: wssbpbsh]
[ar:Disturbed]
[ti:Crucified]
[al:Asylum]
[by:FlaZ]

[00:06.42]Crucified
[00:09.24][00:49.56][01:30.81][02:14.76][02:49.09][03:19.78][03:52.54]
[00:20.30]When others left before
[00:22.37]I could never turn away
[00:24.86]Now that it’s come to this
[00:27.24]Is there nothing left to say?
[00:29.68]I’ve never known before
[00:31.99]Such exquisite suffering
[00:34.43]As I watched you walk away
[00:36.99]I gave into panicking
[00:39.55][01:58.07]I can’t believe that
[00:41.93]This is really happening
[00:44.43]Am I really lost again?
[00:46.80]Desperation drives me insane
[00:52.31]I will focus all the pain
[00:55.81][02:16.26][03:21.59]Right into your heart
[01:00.93][02:19.32][03:24.60]Till it makes you blind
[01:05.31][02:23.63][03:29.10][03:55.58]Till the faces of your former world
[01:08.69][02:26.88][03:32.22][03:58.46]Have fallen from your sight
[01:14.19][02:32.01][03:37.22]Till you’re mine and to the voice
[01:19.25][02:37.59][03:43.16][04:10.76]I tell no longer dominate your mind
[01:24.81][02:44.53][03:50.10][04:03.25][04:16.14]I’m crucified
[01:38.44]Cold and unwhole again
[01:40.69]Crying out and questioning
[01:43.13]Will I ever love again?
[01:45.50]What’s the point of anything?
[01:48.00]It takes a toll again
[01:50.38]This is where the fun begins
[01:52.81]Visions haunt me through the night
[01:55.50]Now I’m dying for your sins
[02:00.19]If you look me in the face
[02:02.69]You can say there’s nothing left
[02:05.13]Our silence drives me insane
[02:07.82]I will focus all my pain
[03:01.78]I cannot feel anything
[03:02.84]And you’re ripe and hot
[03:04.59]Although you’re married to the cross
[03:06.03][03:11.72]Upon it I will remain
[03:07.53]I can’t feel anything
[03:08.66]Which inside is festering
[03:10.15]You nearly took the cross
[03:16.72]I will focus on my pain
[03:52.83][04:05.06]Blind
[04:07.32]And to the voice
