[id: hbhbwqqz]
[ar:Disturbed]
[ti:Enough]
[al:Indestructible]
[00:00.00]Brought to you by Etched_In_Blood
[00:05.00][00:16.00][02:24.64]
[00:08.00]Artist: Disturbed
[00:11.00]Album:  Indestructible
[00:14.00]Title: Enough
[00:18.40](We are frozen, We want everything)
[00:23.33](We’ve chosen to want everything)
[00:29.20]We don't want them, we want everything
[00:31.75]We’ve stolen in this suffering
[00:34.70]And we told them to want everything
[00:37.31]But use caution in what you believe
[00:40.43]And we’re haunted, deny everything
[00:43.23]Controlling in this suffering
[00:46.04]When they’re broken, and lost everything
[00:48.92]They're so much easier to lead
[00:53.22][01:50.41]Take their hope away
[00:56.03][01:53.16]Take their life away
[00:58.71][01:55.98]Leave them nothing left inside
[01:02.52][01:59.56][03:25.39]When your own have died
[01:05.27][02:02.44][03:05.27][03:28.08]When there's no more pride
[01:08.01][02:05.32][03:08.09][03:30.99]When your soul is frozen
[01:11.63][01:22.55][02:08.62][02:19.99][03:11.41][03:22.94][03:34.18][03:45.67]Is that enough?
[01:13.82][02:10.81][03:13.83][03:36.75]When your heart is broken
[01:16.93][02:14.24][03:17.01][03:39.80]A thousand times
[01:19.80][03:19.95][03:42.86]With every moment
[01:37.82]Without warning, we take everything
[01:40.37]Undaunted in this suffering
[01:43.37]The dark forces surround everything
[01:46.19]Make it impossible to see
[02:17.11]With every moment?
[02:47.10]Did they even have a reason why countless sons and daughters had to die
[02:55.80]Can’t you even comprehend the pain
[02:59.98]Tell me when your
[03:03.09]Own have died
