[id: klpopksh]
[ar:disturbed]
[ti:The Animal]
[al:Asylum]
[00:03.21]Artist: Disturbed
[00:09.89]Album: Asylum
[00:17.19]Title: The Animal
[00:30.75][01:22.71][01:43.48][02:24.44][02:46.82][03:19.09][03:38.70]
[00:50.11]I can feel the animal inside
[00:53.91]My resolve is weakening
[00:55.41]Pounding on the doors of my mind
[00:58.41]It’s nearly overpowering
[01:00.34]I cannot begin to describe
[01:03.28]The hunger that I feel again
[01:05.21]Run if you intend to survive
[01:08.22]For the beast is coming to life
[01:12.34][02:14.21]Taking more than a glimmer of this tainted moonlight
[01:17.64][02:19.51]Death approaches on this night
[01:22.96][02:24.69][03:19.35][03:39.08]For the animal’s soul is mine
[01:27.40][02:29.25][03:23.72]We will be completed right before your eyes
[01:32.22][02:34.11][03:28.47]I have no control this time
[01:36.40][02:38.20][03:32.71][03:52.57]And now we both shall dine in Hell tonight
[01:52.16]I can feel the calling again
[01:55.30]The primal need is filling me
[01:57.22]Changes are about to begin
[02:00.34]And now my blood is boiling
[02:02.15]I can see the fear in your eyes
[02:05.27]But you can’t bring yourself to scream
[02:07.21]Time to shed the mortal disguise
[02:10.20]The beast is coming to life
[03:01.81]We begin the hunt tonight
[03:03.68]Til the power courses the creatures take flight
[03:06.37]When the kill is close and I will be satisfied
[03:11.23]For the smell of fear tonight
[03:13.42]Wakes an ancient lust that will not be denied
[03:18.03]You’re mine
[03:43.52]And the world around will never hear your cries
[03:48.20]An unholy crime
