[id: bpblwvqn]
[offset:12]
[ar:Disturbed]
[ti:Meaning of Life]
[al:The Sickness]
[by:Draiman]
[00:00.01]Artist: Disturbed

[00:06.06]Album: The Sickness

[00:12.11]Title: Meaning of Life


[00:18.16][00:42.31][00:45.80][00:49.78][01:39.23][01:43.01][01:46.79][01:50.73][02:40.27][03:25.94][03:42.79][03:58.70]
[00:39.62][00:47.38][01:41.31][01:48.74][03:43.63]Get psycho
[00:43.66][00:53.00][01:44.69][01:54.46][03:33.35][03:46.75]I wanna get psycho
[00:51.06][01:52.41]I wanna
[00:51.91][00:52.31][01:52.91][01:53.46][01:53.91][03:41.52][03:42.07][03:56.69][03:57.31][03:58.10]wanna
[00:55.01]Run you little bitch
[00:56.58]I want your power glowing, juicy flowing, red hot, meaning of life
[01:01.22]It's not enough to have a little taste
[01:04.12][02:05.06]I want the whole damn thing now
[01:06.71][02:07.72]Can you dig it?
[01:08.55][02:09.52]Need to get psycho
[01:10.44]wanna hear you say it
[01:11.97]say, you want it, need it
[01:13.88]Don't wanna wait until we finish the show
[01:16.43]It's not enough, you hunger for more
[01:19.11][02:20.14]You're one twisted little fuck
[01:21.34]And now you anna get psycho with me
[01:23.89][01:24.71][01:27.13][01:27.83][01:28.58][01:30.91][01:31.66][01:32.31][01:34.79][01:35.50][01:36.19][01:38.49][02:25.09][02:25.70][02:28.04][02:28.79][02:29.49][02:31.77][02:32.57][02:33.32][02:35.72][02:36.36][02:37.02][02:39.45]Give in
[01:25.46][01:29.27][01:33.10][01:36.79][02:26.45][02:30.24][02:34.02][02:37.81]Decide
[01:56.15]Scratch my itch
[01:57.55]Give me your power glowing, juicy flowing red hot, meaning of life
[02:02.28]It's not enough to have a little piece
[02:11.37]Wanna hear you scream
[02:12.75]Tell me to take you, scare you, fuck you
[02:15.40]After we finish the show
[02:17.44]It's not enough, you listening whore?
[02:22.23]And now you wanna get psycho with me
[02:55.37]I can feel the blood flowing through my veins spilling on my soul
[02:57.09]And now the hunger’s getting bigger
[02:59.49]Come a little closer now pretentious whore and pull my trigger
[03:03.48]Free the violence that is building in me
[03:06.07]I say now end of the ride murder suicide is how I’ve been feeling lately
[03:10.67][03:14.59][03:18.37]Come a little closer now pretentious whore,
[03:12.28][03:16.03][03:19.92]I’m reeling with a feeling that I
[03:13.73][03:17.50][03:21.19]Can’t ignore
[03:21.78]And the need to get psycho
[03:24.05]Is not a question to me
[03:27.59][03:31.85][03:35.72][03:45.03][03:48.86]Get
[03:28.16][03:28.61][03:29.16][03:32.30][03:32.85][03:36.17][03:36.83][03:37.33][03:39.33][03:40.03][03:40.53][03:45.67][03:46.17][03:49.41][03:50.08][03:50.64][03:52.89][03:53.40][03:53.89]get
[03:30.25][03:37.93][03:51.20]get psycho
[03:41.16]i wanna
[03:54.49]i wanna get psycho
[03:56.39]Wanna
