[id: azvvzoqz]
[ar:Disturbed]
[ti:Torn]
[al:Indestructible]
[00:00.00]Artist: Disturbed
[00:00.00]Album:  Indestructible
[00:00.00]Title: Torn
[00:00.00]By:  Nova0001
[00:00.00][02:17.47]
[00:11.53]I’m without fault today, didn’t think it would kill you
[00:16.59]To settle the debt I thought never would be paid
[00:21.59]Found out I was wrong today, too weak to continue
[00:27.20]One final defense to fall
[00:29.31]Still I’m broken
[00:30.91][01:33.15][02:56.91]Now I am torn, thought it was over this time
[00:38.25][01:40.21][03:03.82][03:25.43]And we know there’s still a fire inside
[00:45.37][01:47.63][03:11.14][03:32.47]And we know, and we know
[00:51.99][01:54.62][03:39.28]We’re gonna let it burn
[00:59.85][02:02.05][03:46.88]Let it burn
[01:05.10][02:07.41][03:52.26]T’ill the image fades away
[01:13.69]You made(?) a price to pay, didn’t think it would thrill you
[01:18.80]To witness the fallen ones shattered and ashamed
[01:24.33]No I’m not the only one with a need to fulfill you
[01:29.62]The one willing to risk it all
[01:32.08]Still uncertain
[02:13.84]YEEAAaahhhhaaaaaaaa!!
[02:17.66]/Guitar solo/
[03:18.12]That I am torn, thought it was over this time
