[id: uwqzvlsu]
[ar:Disturbed]
[ti:Old Friend]
[al:B-Side Asylum]
[by:D00msday]
[00:00.00][00:37.60][01:09.48][01:40.43][02:11.51][02:47.00][03:17.49][03:20.61][03:27.65][03:29.48]
[00:13.57]They are the ghosts of innocence
[00:17.00]That have awoken from my dreams
[00:20.25]Welcome to your nightmare
[00:23.24][03:24.54]Say goodbye to everything
[00:26.45]All your past obscenities
[00:29.48]They have determined where I stand
[00:32.75]Echoing cries, in the time that it began, yahh!
[00:38.30][01:41.75]Hear me now
[00:42.22][01:44.68]Feel my plea!
[00:46.25][01:48.30][02:54.27]There is no more time for apologies
[00:52.14][01:54.41][03:00.38]Never let emotions
[00:54.51][01:56.91][03:02.76]Take hold of me!
[00:58.50][02:00.72][03:06.69]Are you ready to begin your trip to the other side?
[01:05.87][02:08.14][03:13.99]Death is an old friend of mine
[01:16.28]You can’t escape your judgment
[01:19.59]I hear them calling out your name
[01:22.53]Do not beg for mercy now
[01:25.64]You never showed any to them
[01:28.83]Embrace your final punishment
[01:31.82]There’s not a soul to hear you scream
[01:34.88]I have to thank you for letting out the animal in me, yahh!
[02:21.00]The blood became alive
[02:22.85]When I was trapped inside
[02:24.42]And I can feel the dark passenger coming
[02:27.62]My mother’s blood and mine
[02:29.06]Uniquely intertwined
[02:30.56]Help me father put your memory from my mind
[02:33.80]My hunger to destroy
[02:35.24]When I was just a boy
[02:36.80]It pulled deeper into something that I now enjoy
[02:40.05]The ritual begins
[02:41.54]Evil will meet it’s end
[02:42.98]In your destruction I will finally feel whole again
[03:18.22]I have become your nightmare
[03:29.17]Rah!
