[id: svnuaish]
[ar:Disturbed]
[ti:Another Way To Die]
[al:Asylum]
[by:hariks]
[00:02.95]by hariks (soad.hariks@gmail.com) UA Telesweet
[00:05.69][00:55.72][01:12.10][03:05.05]

[00:19.52]The indulgence of our lives has cast a shadow on our world.
[00:27.52]Our devotion to our appetites betrayed us all.
[00:36.72]An apocalyptic plight.
[00:40.32]More destruction will unfold.
[00:44.82]Mother Earth will show her darker side and take her toll.
[01:07.62][02:05.32][02:58.92][03:56.72][04:05.42]It's just another way to die.
[01:18.02]There can be another reason why.
[01:20.32]You know we should have seen it coming.
[01:22.62]Consequences we cannot deny will be revealed in time.
[01:26.32]Glaciers melt as we pollute the sky.
[01:28.82]A sign of devastation coming.
[01:30.72]We don’t need another way to die.
[01:33.62][02:09.72][04:01.12][04:10.02]Can we repent in time?
[01:35.12]The Time bomb is ticking and no one is listening.
[01:38.92][02:32.52]Our future is fading.
[01:41.22][02:34.82]Is there any hope we’ll survive?
[01:45.52][02:39.32][03:37.12]Still, we ravage the world that we love.
[01:51.62]And the millions cry out to be saved.
[01:56.12][02:49.82][03:47.32]Our endless maniacal appetite.
[02:00.62][02:54.22][03:51.82]Left us with another way to die.
[02:11.82]Greed and hunger led to our demise.
[02:13.82]A path I can’t believe we followed.
[02:16.02]Black agenda’s rooted in a lie.
[02:18.62]Will we repent in time?
[02:19.92]Species fall before our very eyes.
[02:22.32]A world that they cannot survive in left them with another way to die.
[02:27.32]Are we dead inside?
[02:28.72]The time bomb is ticking and no one is listening.
[02:45.02][03:43.02]And millions cry out to be saved.


