[ar: Disturbed]
[ti: Indestructible]
[Encoding: iso-8859-15]
[id: hwhowhqz]
[00:54.24]Another mission

[00:55.59]The powers have called me away

[00:56.56]Another time

[00:57.40]To carry the colors again

[00:59.17]My motivation

[00:59.79]An oath I’ve sworn to defend

[01:01.79]To win the honor

[01:02.82]Of coming back home again

[01:04.51]No explanation

[01:05.43]Will matter after we begin

[01:07.28]Another dark destroyer that’s buried in me

[01:09.98]My true vocation

[01:10.61]And now my unfortunate friend

[01:12.50]You will discover

[01:13.31]A war you’re unable to win


[01:15.21]I'll have you know

[01:18.68]That I’ve become…


[01:20.31]Indestructible
[01:21.67]Determination that is incorruptible
[01:24.46]From the other side
[01:25.55]A terror to behold
[01:26.95]Annihilation will be unavoidable
[01:29.81]Every broken enemy will know
[01:32.53]That their opponent get to be invincible
[01:35.16]Take a last look around while you’re alive
[01:38.19]I’m an indestructible master of war
[01:51.29]Another reason
[01:51.97]Another cause for me to fight
[01:53.73]Another fuse uncovered
[01:55.12]Now, for me to light
[01:56.58]My dedication
[01:57.84]To all that I’ve sworn to protect
[01:59.14]I carry out my orders
[02:00.60]With not a regret
[02:01.86]A declaration
[02:02.95]Embedded deep under my skin
[02:04.54]A permanent reminder
[02:05.94]Of how we began
[02:07.25]No hesitation
[02:08.33]When I am commanding the strike
[02:09.82]You need to know
[02:10.78]That you’re in for the fight of your life
[02:14.33]You will be shown
[02:16.01]How I've become....
[02:17.59]Indestructible
[02:19.06]Determination that is incorruptible
[02:21.85]From the other side
[02:23.01]A terror to behold
[02:24.48]Annihilation will be unavoidable
[02:26.99]Every broken enemy will know
[02:29.56]That their opponent get to be invincible
[02:32.12]Take a last look around while you’re alive
[02:35.43]I’m an indestructible master of war
[03:19.18]Indestructible
[03:20.43]Determination that is incorruptible
[03:23.08]From the other side
[03:24.23]A terror to behold
[03:25.67]Annihilation will be unavoidable
[03:28.21]Every broken enemy will know
[03:31.18]That their opponent had to be invincible
[03:33.76]Take a last look around while you’re alive
[03:36.54]I am indestructible (indestructible)
[03:38.91]Indestructible

[03:41.84]Determination that is incorruptible

[03:44.40]From the other side

[03:45.62]A terror to behold

[03:47.26]Annihilation will be unavoidable

[03:49.66]Every broken enemy will know


[03:52.53]That their opponent had to be invincible
[03:55.02]Take a last look around while you’re alive

[03:58.47]I’m an indestructible master of war




















































