[id: iiviswqw]
[ar:Disturbed]
[ti:Parasite]
[al:Indestructible]
[by:SinPlayer]

[00:01.22]Disturbed - Parasite
[00:05.65]by SinPlayer
[00:12.15][00:47.51][00:55.77][01:14.42][01:38.05][01:44.90][02:03.16][02:13.60][02:43.03][02:56.03][03:07.90]
[00:12.53][Verse 1]
[00:24.16][03:08.84]You’ve got nowhere to hide,
[00:26.10][03:10.03]And all bullshit aside,
[00:27.41]You've committed a terrible crime.
[00:30.22][03:14.22]You’ve stepped over the line and
[00:31.84][03:16.09]You’d better be running for your life.
[00:36.04]Fucked over again,
[00:37.59]I even called you a friend,
[00:39.10]A mistake I won’t be repeating,
[00:41.97]I just don’t understand,
[00:43.51]How you can even continue to deny!
[00:47.39][01:39.75]You know why,
[00:47.88][01:39.24][Hook]
[00:49.64][01:42.41]Don’t you pretend that you don’t know why,
[00:56.99][01:49.53]Because you’re living through association,
[00:57.39][01:46.16][Chorus]
[01:01.55][02:35.21]Has been getting you high!
[01:04.92][01:57.65]You sell your soul,
[01:07.24][01:59.91][02:41.34]For just a taste of the life!
[01:16.00][Verse 2]
[01:17.18]Now what a surprise, to discover the lies,
[01:19.99]You’ll be telling again in no time.
[01:22.87]You just don’t realize they’ll come back
[01:25.24]And be fucking up your life!
[01:28.67]In trouble again, I just don’t understand,
[01:31.68]This whole pattern that keeps repeating.
[01:34.62]You know you’ll do it again,
[01:36.24]And admit you can step into the light!
[01:54.22]Isn’t getting you high!
[02:03.91]Determination, isn’t running on high,
[02:09.04][02:49.96]No control, for just a taste of the life!
[02:32.34]Cuz your association,
[02:38.59]You sell your soul
[02:44.78]Determination has been running on high!
[03:04.72]For just a taste of the life…
[03:11.47]You’ve committed a terrible crime.
