[id: quacpbsh]
[ar:Disturbed]
[ti:Leave It Alone]
[al:Asylum]
[by:FlaZ]
[00:00.00][00:08.44][00:47.19][01:24.56][02:01.44][02:39.37][03:07.96][03:46.58]
[00:03.81]Leave It Alone
[00:18.69]I can’t control my anger and
[00:21.60]I’ve been about to explode
[00:23.78]Far too many times
[00:25.53]I’ve seen my dreams becoming violent
[00:29.16]Every time that I see you
[00:32.56]No matter how you try to define it
[00:36.81]I have been broken too many times
[00:40.06]Too much emotion too long confined has
[00:44.62]Weakened the wall that protects you
[00:47.57][02:01.75][03:09.21]Ease your mind, this moment will pass if you just
[00:53.13][02:07.62][03:15.22]Leave it alone, leave it alone every time
[00:58.44][02:13.00][03:20.10]My dysfunction is on your mind
[01:02.75][02:17.06][03:24.10]When you find that you’re at odds with your desire
[01:07.75][02:22.24][03:29.41]Just leave it alone, leave it alone every time
[01:12.82][02:27.37][03:34.54]My destruction is on your mind
[01:17.07][02:31.56][03:38.47]Before you find that you have
[01:19.87][02:34.50][03:42.00]Tested my resolve one too many times
[01:33.18]I am a stranger, you know I’ve been
[01:36.31]Pressed to the wall far too many times
[01:40.12]Stop your behavior or you will find
[01:43.62]My murderous nature surround you
[01:46.93]Others have wandered over the line that
[01:51.18]Awaken the monster too many times
[01:54.62]Leave it unspoken and you will find an
[01:58.37]End to the violence if you can
[02:40.46]______________
