[id: qscbpbsh]
[ar:Disturbed]
[ti:My Child]
[al:Asylum]
[by:FlaZ]
[00:00.00][00:08.31][00:52.69][01:16.63][01:48.84][02:12.72][02:37.21][03:00.66]
[00:04.37]My Child
[00:21.31]Tore it up again, I couldn’t stop again
[00:23.62]Letting go till there was nothing in the way
[00:26.31]Fuck the feeling then, I cave in again
[00:28.93]Sweet surrender to the angel I deny
[00:31.50]When you came to life I was terrified
[00:34.25]I knew that nothing else would ever feel the same
[00:36.93]Doubt came over me; what kind of father would I be?
[00:39.69]Another time I could stand up and be a man
[00:44.06][01:39.56]To change a face in my life
[00:46.44][01:42.37]Your future and mine
[00:49.00][01:45.06]Time to do what is right
[00:51.38][01:46.59]A new beginning
[00:52.94][01:49.09][02:37.52]The world around me died
[00:55.62][01:51.72][02:39.58]When I saw that heartbeat
[00:58.00][01:54.03][02:41.90]I knew it wasn’t a sin
[01:03.57][01:59.16][02:47.33]Can someone tell me why
[01:06.19][02:02.16][02:50.15]This has happened to me?
[01:08.69][02:04.59][02:52.46]Why was it only in death
[01:11.88][02:07.72][02:56.02]Would you redeem my child?
[01:17.32]No serenity within agony
[01:19.46]Every day brings on
[01:21.21]A hundred ways to fight
[01:22.34]Constant scrutiny
[01:23.61]I can feel you judging me
[01:24.87]Resurrecting every demon that’s inside
[01:27.55]The priest was horrified
[01:28.86]You struggled for the life
[01:30.24]That one desire was
[01:31.74]The dream I sought for yours
[01:32.93]Creeps cripple me, the reaper kidded me
[01:35.49]Left me early for the path I’d come to adore
[02:36.25]My child
[03:05.45]I pray you will redeem my child
