[id: qlzhqwsa]
[ar:Lady GaGa]
[ti:Bad Romance (Album Version)]
[al:The Fame Monster]
[00:00.00][00:07.84][01:28.77][01:36.30][02:49.08][02:56.99][04:26.60][04:36.05]Oh-oh-oh-oh-oooh!
[00:03.60][00:11.37][01:31.38][01:39.34][02:53.74][03:00.21][04:38.29]Oh-oh-oooh-oh-oh!
[00:04.91][00:12.76][01:33.06][01:41.21][02:54.31][03:01.89][04:01.10][04:08.25][04:32.15][04:40.40]Caught in a bad romance
[00:07.71][00:16.54][00:25.01][00:33.47][00:46.40][00:48.96][01:05.25][01:13.41][01:28.53][01:36.04][01:44.45][01:53.53][02:08.21][02:25.63][02:33.41][02:48.89][02:56.73][03:05.38][03:13.90][03:21.43][04:42.89]
[00:16.85][01:44.69][03:07.50][03:14.21][04:43.27]Rah-rah-ah-ah-ah!
[00:18.97][00:27.06][01:47.31][03:09.55][03:15.58][04:45.81]Rah-muh-Rah-muh-mah!
[00:21.15][00:28.92][01:48.99][03:10.35][03:17.50][04:47.86]Ga-Ga-ooh-la-la!
[00:23.02][00:30.79][01:51.09][03:11.60][03:19.62][04:50.05]Want your bad romance
[00:25.13]Bah-rah-ah-ah-ah!
[00:33.59]I want your ugly
[00:34.90]I want your disease
[00:37.26]I want your everything as long as it’s free
[00:40.31][01:02.57][02:00.87][02:16.35][02:20.77]I want your love (Love Love Love)
[00:44.42][01:04.38][02:23.32][03:40.00][03:44.17]I want your love
[00:46.78]Yeah!
[00:49.20]I want your drama
[00:50.51]The touch of your hand (Hay!)
[00:53.25]I want your leather studded kiss in the scene
[00:56.36]And I want your love
[00:59.41]You know that I want you (Love Love Love)
[01:05.44]You know that I want you
[01:07.50][02:29.92]And you know that I need you
[01:09.55][02:30.85]I want a bad, a bad romance
[01:13.65][01:21.05][02:33.65][02:42.36][04:12.42][04:20.33]I want your loving
[01:14.71][02:35.08][03:41.94][04:13.73]And I want your revenge
[01:16.88][01:24.67][02:36.70][02:44.98][04:15.53][04:23.80]You and me could write a bad romance
[01:22.79][02:43.48]All your lovers' revenge
[01:53.72]I want your horror
[01:55.09]I want your design
[01:57.63]‘Cause you’re a criminal
[01:59.19]As long as your mine
[02:04.61]I want your love (Ugh)
[02:08.52]I want your Psycho
[02:11.14]Your Vertigo stick (Hay!)
[02:13.62]Want you in my Rear Window, baby your sick
[02:25.82]You know that I want you (Cause I'm A Free Bitch Baby)
[03:22.87][03:26.97][03:31.08][03:35.45]Walk walk fashion baby, Work it
[03:25.05][03:29.27][03:33.26]Move that bitch crazy
[03:37.88]I'm a free bitch baby
[03:46.22]I don’t wanna be friends
[03:48.28]Je veux ton amour et je veux ta revanche
[03:52.64]Je veux ton amour, I don't wanna be friends
[03:58.86]I don't wanna be friends
[04:02.78]I don't wanna be friends!
[04:06.70][04:10.37][04:29.45][04:34.49]Want your bad romance!
[04:22.00]and all your lovers' revenge


