[id: wksnnhsh]
[ar:Linkin Park]
[ti:Wretches and Kings]
[al:A Thousand Suns]
[00:00.41]There’s a time when the operation of the machine
[00:03.08]becomes so odious, makes you so sick at heart,
[00:07.39]that you can’t take part,
[00:09.63][03:29.98]you can’t even passively take part,
[00:11.94]and you’ve got to put your bodies
[00:13.63]on the gears and upon the wheels,
[00:15.87]upon the levers, upon all the apparatus,
[00:17.68]and you’ve got to make it stop!
[00:20.75][00:38.71][01:16.04][01:34.36][02:15.11][02:27.59][02:38.69][03:21.55][03:51.88]
[00:22.12]Artist: Linkin Park
[00:25.36]Album: A Thousand Suns
[00:29.54]Title: Wretches and Kings
[00:33.53]By: Linkin Park
[00:40.83]To save face
[00:42.02]How low can you go?
[00:43.77]Talk a lot of game but yet you don’t know
[00:46.45]Static on the way make us all say whoa
[00:49.07]The people up top push the people down low
[00:51.63]Get down and obey every word
[00:54.19]Steady, get in line if you haven’t yet heard
[00:57.19]Want to take what I got?
[00:58.32]Don’t be absurd
[00:59.49]Don’t fight the power and nobody gets hurt
[01:01.88]If you haven’t heard yet than I’m letting you know
[01:04.69]There ain’t shit we don’t run when guns unload
[01:07.25]And no one make a move unless my people say so
[01:10.30]Got everything under control
[01:11.93][02:05.93]Now everybody go
[01:23.72][02:16.98]Feel alone, final blow
[01:26.34][02:19.60]We the animals take control
[01:28.96][02:22.53]Hear us now, clear and tall
[01:31.99][02:25.47]Wretches and kings
[01:33.24][02:26.53]We come for you
[01:34.59]So keep face
[01:35.47]How slow can you go?
[01:37.28]Talk a lot of shit and yet you don’t know
[01:39.97]Fire on the way make you all say whoa
[01:42.52]The people up top and the people down low
[01:44.95]Get down and I’m running it like that
[01:47.82]The front of the attack is exactly where I’m at
[01:50.63]Somewhere in between and kicking the hi-hat
[01:53.02]The pen and the contract, the pitch and the contact
[01:55.76]So get with the combat
[01:57.51]I’m letting them know
[01:58.57]There ain’t shit you can say to make me back down low
[02:01.13]So push the button and the whole thing blows
[02:03.75]Spinning everything out of control
[02:27.84]Still alone, fight our blow
[02:30.33]Filthy animals beat down low
[02:33.14]Steel and bone, black and blue
[02:35.84]Run on the sunshine
[02:37.25]We come to you
[02:48.98]From the front to back
[02:50.60][02:55.98][03:01.33][03:06.82][03:11.94][03:17.18]And the side to side
[02:51.79][02:57.28][03:02.64][03:07.95][03:13.25][03:18.62]If you feel what I feel
[02:53.22][02:58.71][03:03.89][03:09.13][03:14.69][03:19.93]Put them up real high
[02:54.84][03:00.02][03:05.26][03:10.69][03:16.06]Front to back
[03:21.86]When the operation of the machine becomes so odious,
[03:25.54]makes you so sick at heart, that you can’t take part,
[03:32.10]and you’ve got to put your bodies on the gears
[03:35.03]and upon the wheels, upon the levers,
[03:37.46]upon all the apparatus, and you’ve got to make it stop!
[03:40.52]And you’ve got to indicate to the people who run it,
[03:43.08]to the people who own it, that unless you’re free,
[03:45.14]the machine will be prevented from working at all!
[03:59.68]sincronized by raph.mello
