[id: upowonqz]
[ar:Lordi]
[ti:To Hell With Pop]
[al:Blood Red Sandman]
[00:00.00]Artist: Lordi
[00:02.40]Single: Blood Red Sandman
[00:04.31]Title: To Hell With Pop
[00:06.26]By:  [•~Ð-devil~•]
[00:08.30][00:33.90][00:47.41][01:12.83][01:46.63][02:13.70][02:39.00][03:06.90][03:21.25][03:48.32] 
[00:21.10]Some want it soft
[00:22.75]Some want it hard
[00:27.82]Some like it slow
[00:29.46]Some like it fast as the shark
[00:34.32]You hate it every single way
[00:38.16]You really need no room to play
[00:41.35]You make it so damn hard to stay
[00:47.80][00:50.10][00:55.30][00:56.76][02:14.09][02:16.44][02:21.48][02:23.13]Run away
[00:52.50][02:18.79]Ooh, you better run away
[00:59.27][02:25.48]Run before it's too late
[01:01.94][02:28.08]The truth is right behind you
[01:04.63][02:30.74]Closing in... on you!
[01:08.73][02:34.79]So run away
[01:13.25][02:39.39][03:48.71]You ain't nobody's nightmare
[01:16.49][02:42.63][03:51.82]You weren't boiled in flames
[01:20.59][02:46.83][03:55.97]You ain't no Devil's daughter
[01:23.28][02:49.29][03:58.35]You don't know her pain
[01:27.43][02:53.49][04:02.60]There's no 7-headed demons
[01:29.78][02:55.74][04:05.06]No lakes above the ground
[01:33.89][02:59.95][04:09.16]But on the day of black sun rises, see
[01:36.84][03:02.95][04:12.22]It's you who's going down
[01:39.19]To hell with the pop
[01:47.05]You wipe the smile right off your face
[01:54.13]That leads to higher 'bout to holy ways
[02:00.84]You think your fashion seems you fine
[02:04.29]You're much not worth for single die
[02:07.40]You will be flow down for your crimes
[03:07.29][04:14.62]To hell with the pop!
[03:21.67][Solo]
[04:17.26]AW!
