[id: iohisoqi]
[ar:Lordi]
[ti:Who's Your Daddy]
[al:The Arockalypse]




[00:04.04]Lordi - Who's Your Daddy
[00:05.25][02:22.27]---
[00:14.81][01:08.30]OH! Yeahyeahyeahyeah
[00:21.33][00:37.60][00:42.71][00:52.07][01:07.59][01:14.06][01:23.67][01:31.01][01:39.50][02:07.61]-
[00:28.50]All the vixens stand in line
[00:32.10]Waiting for my fright night
[00:35.63]Be the new flesh for the sacrifice
[00:38.92][01:24.73]Screaming out the mating call
[00:41.10][01:27.17]I´ve become the lord of love
[00:46.36][01:32.67]I break your will,
[00:47.47][01:33.73]I´ll break your will for good
[00:49.34]I treat you like a brute
[00:53.14][01:00.37][02:08.16][02:11.44][02:14.98]Who´s your daddy,
[00:54.70][02:09.48]say , who´s you daddy?
[00:56.72]Who puts you in your place?
[01:01.93]bitch, who´s your daddy?
[01:03.74]Surrender and obey, who´s your daddy?
[01:14.52]She´s a battle-ax in pinstripes
[01:17.90]Get ready for your prime time
[01:21.39]Max out the triple-X drive
[01:36.01]Treat you like a brute
[01:53.95]Get down, get down
[01:55.42]Lay down, lay down
[01:57.19]Stay down, stay down
[01:59.57]for daddy
[02:06.39]UH! UH!
[02:12.92]girl , who´s you daddy?
[02:16.61]bitch , who´s you daddy?
[02:18.58]Who keeps you in line?
[03:36.13]END








