[id: vqispzqw]
[ar:Lordi]
[ti:Bite It Like A Bulldog]
[al:Deadache]
[by:[•~Ð-devil~•]]
[00:28.91]Caught red handed
[00:30.53]Blood drops cover your face
[00:32.36]The gun's still smoking in your hand
[00:36.02]You did not do it
[00:37.17]The rest of the world is always wrong
[00:40.01]As you see it from where you stand
[00:43.23][01:40.52]Always try to find another fall guy
[00:45.42][01:42.82]Sacrifice your mother
[00:47.04][01:44.43]The pawns don't know that they're in your game
[00:50.54][01:47.70]Anybody really will do fine as long as it won't be you
[00:54.23][01:51.54]You let the dice decide who's to blame
[00:57.33][01:54.80][03:00.96][03:15.46](you)Bite it, bite it like a bulldog
[00:59.68][01:57.10][03:03.26][03:17.68]Bite it like a bulldog to the bone
[01:02.58][02:00.00][03:06.32][03:20.58]Never let it go
[01:04.70][02:02.04][02:53.72][03:08.30]Bite it, bite it like a bulldog
[01:07.00][02:04.34][03:10.50]Bite it like a bulldog freaking out
[01:09.85][02:07.21][03:13.45]Foaming at the mouth
[01:26.30]You won't take no responsibility
[01:29.39]For anything you say or do
[01:33.25]Friend or foe, it don't matter anyone can go
[01:36.86]As long as it won't be you
[02:11.30]You leave a trail of dead behind you
[02:18.30]You're dead wrong but you aren't givin in
[02:25.48]To deny the truth don't make it untrue
[02:32.20]Just saying it don't make you a kingpin
[02:52.39]Bite it, bite it like a
[02:57.29]Bite it to the bone, never let it go
[03:06.30] 
