[id: kqqqulsh]
[ar:Lunatica]
[ti:Time]
[al:Atlantis]
[by:尊]
[00:00.00]歌手：Lunatica
[00:02.00]专辑：Atlantis
[00:04.00]【Time】
[00:06.00]歌词：尊
[00:08.00][01:17.97][01:24.92][02:40.45][03:01.24][03:13.59]
[00:15.30]Autumn has come, I’m loosing my leaves
[00:30.26]The sand has almost ran through
[00:58.53][02:21.08]Run, run, run for eternal youth
[01:05.61][02:28.13]I must escape from my faith
[01:11.58][02:34.15]There is no bribery to make the mirror lie
[01:18.97][02:42.27]Run, run, run, run
[01:22.20][02:47.96]The air is getting thin [x2]

[01:40.66]In my life’s opera, they play the final notes
[01:52.93]The happy tunes turned to minor
[03:02.84]solo
[03:15.69]Time is hunting me, there is no way out
[03:22.85]My winter will come
[03:44.27]A long time ago the orchard in me has whithered
