[id: hhauqosa]
[ar:LUNATICA]
[ti:THE LANDING]
[al:ATLANTIS]
[Refr:]
[00:01.70]Artist: LUNATICA
[00:04.75]Album: ATLANTIS
[00:08.63]Title: THE LANDING
[00:12.37]By: TzaxorT  -- Black Angel
[00:17.92]Offset: 0
[00:19.23][00:49.62][00:53.11][00:55.30][00:58.98][00:59.41][01:01.47][01:34.32][01:35.81][02:19.05][02:31.96][02:48.82]
[00:19.61]Don’t turn away from her, liar, you promised to beware her from argue

[00:27.22]It’s the only way to save your mortal soul

[00:34.34]Her vivid expressions, the detailed report of things that will be

[00:41.82]Are throwing a spell over you
[00:58.53][02:55.66][03:25.92]Hear her prophecies
[01:01.46][02:58.34][03:28.40]Open your heart and mind
[01:07.35][03:03.90][03:34.27]to her hypnotic voice

[01:13.08][03:10.32][03:40.57]Believe and you’ll see the truth

[01:16.12][03:13.07][03:43.28]But don’t let hatred reign your life

[01:36.62]She’s gifted with the eye and dreams of genocide

[01:44.79]Once you cried with her, after sleeping in her bed

[01:52.09]Now you're blinded by the fire of ignorance

[01:59.51]That people lit in your miserable heart
[02:34.40]"arcangel.diabolico@hotmail.com"




[03:57.41]visit    msms.tk






