[ar: Eminem]
[ti: Lose Yourself]
[al: 8 Mile (Sound Track)]
[Encoding: iso-8859-15]
[id: kskiziss]
[00:00.00]Artist: Eminem
[00:05.00]Title: Lose Yourself
[00:10.00]
[00:15.00]
[00:30.70]
[00:36.68]Look, if you had one shot, or one opportunity
[00:46.12]To seize everything you ever wanted-One moment
[00:50.95]Would you capture it or just let it slip
[00:54.91]Yo, His palms are sweaty, knees weak, arms are heavy
[00:59.37]There's vomit on his sweater already, mom's spaghetti
[01:01.67]He's nervous, but on the surface he looks calm and ready
[01:04.37]To drop bombs, but he keeps on forgetting
[01:07.26]What he wrote down, the whole crowd goes so loud
[01:10.18]He opens his mouth, but the words won't come out
[01:12.38]He's chokin, how everybody's chokin now
[01:15.57]The clock's run out, time's up over, bloah!
[01:18.38]Snap back to reality, Oh there goes gravity
[01:21.37]Oh, there goes Rabbit, he choked
[01:23.90]He's so mad, but he won't give up that easy
[01:25.65]No, he won't have it , he knows his whole back city's ropes
[01:28.77]It don't matter, he's dope
[01:30.37]He knows that, but he's broke
[01:31.77]He's so stacked that he knows
[01:33.02]When he goes back to his mobile home, that's when it's
[01:35.63]Back to the lab again yo
[01:37.06]This whole rap city
[01:38.54]He better go capture this moment and hope it don't pass him
[01:41.48][Chorus]
[01:41.74]You better lose yourself in the music, the moment
[01:43.92]You own it, you better never let it go
[01:46.23]You only get one shot, do not miss your chance to blow
[01:49.32]This opportunity comes once in a lifetime,
[01:52.42]You better lose yourself in the music, the moment
[01:54.99]You own it, you better never let it go
[01:57.12]You only get one shot, do not miss your chance to blow
[02:00.21]This opportunity comes once in a lifetime you better,
[02:03.24]His soul's escaping, through this hole that it's gaping
[02:06.21]This world is mine for the taking
[02:08.56]Make me king, as we move toward a, new world order
[02:11.92]A normal life is borin, but superstardom's close to post mortom
[02:15.01]It only grows harder, only grows hotter
[02:17.70]He blows us all over these hoes is all on him
[02:21.62]Coast to coast shows, he's know as the globetrotter
[02:24.46]Lonely roads, God only knows
[02:26.21]He's grown farther from home, he's no father
[02:28.32]He goes home and barely knows his own daughter
[02:31.31]But hold your nose cause here goes the cold water
[02:33.92]These ho's don't want him no mo, he's cold product
[02:37.04]They moved on to the next schmoe who flows
[02:39.27]He nose dove and sold nada
[02:41.09]So the soap opera is told and unfolds
[02:42.95]I suppose it¡¦s old partner, but the beat goes on
[02:45.62]Da da dum da dum da da
[02:48.43]You better lose yourself in the music, the moment
[02:50.80]You own it, you better never let it go
[02:53.04]You only get one shot, do not miss your chance to blow
[02:56.41]This opportunity comes once in a lifetime
[02:59.24]You better lose yourself in the music, the moment
[03:01.96]You own it, you better never let it go
[03:04.25]You only get one shot, do not miss your chance to blow
[03:08.04]This opportunity comes once in a lifetime yo, you better
[03:11.24]No more games, I'ma change what you call rage
[03:13.52]Tear this mothafuckin roof off like 2 dogs caged
[03:15.94]I was playin in the beginnin, the mood all changed
[03:18.71]I been chewed up and spit out and booed off stage
[03:21.55]But I kept rhymin and stepwritin the next cypher
[03:24.80]Best believe somebody's payin the pied piper
[03:27.58]All the pain inside amplified by the fact
[03:30.35]That I can't get by with my 9 to 5
[03:33.19]And I can't provide the right type of life for my family
[03:37.02]Cause man, these goddam food stamps don't buy diapers
[03:39.91]And it's no movie, there's no Makai Pfeiffer, this is my life
[03:43.96]And these times are so hard and it's getting even harder
[03:46.71]Tryin to feed and water my seed, plus
[03:48.93]Teeter-totter caught up between trying to be a father and a prima donna
[03:52.29]Baby mama drama's screamin on and
[03:54.61]Too much for me to wanna
[03:55.96]Stay in one spot, another day of monotony
[03:57.93]Has gotten me to the point, I'm like a snail
[04:00.30]I've got to formulate a plot or I end up in jail or shot
[04:03.24]Success is my only mothafuckin option, failure's not
[04:06.80]Mom, I love you, but this trailer's got to go
[04:09.60]I cannot grow old in Salem's lot
[04:11.91]So here I go is my shot.
[04:13.88]Feet fail me not or not this may be the only opportunity that I got
[04:17.50][Chorus]
[04:17.90]You better lose yourself in the music, the moment
[04:20.50]You own it, you better never let it go
[04:22.91]You only get one shot, do not miss your chance to blow
[04:25.83]This opportunity comes once in a lifetime
[04:28.50]
[04:28.72]You better lose yourself in the music, the moment
[04:31.61]You own it, you better never let it go
[04:34.13]You only get one shot, do not miss your chance to blow
[04:37.19]This opportunity comes once in a lifetime you better,
[04:42.55][You can do anything you set your mind to, man]
[04:45.30]

