[id: wubwqcsa]
[ar:Epica]
[ti:White Waters]
[al:Design Your Universe]
[by:Lucyx]
[00:01.66][01:51.20][02:15.24][03:13.56][03:37.65]
[01:29.59]I see a silhouette, liquid that moves
[01:33.67]Skin like a girl in the sea
[01:37.77]I cannot resist this, a voice in the wind
[01:42.17]But is it my eyes I deceit? Is it you I see?
[01:51.26][03:14.00]Lay down in my arms
[01:57.25]Trust what you see
[02:03.16]Smooth your breath, you will be with me
[02:09.33]To find your relief
[02:51.93]Gazing that white path, is coming so close
[02:56.61]Everything is settled with care
[03:00.74]I’m within aching, and still I am waiting
[03:04.88]The water is pulling me near
[03:08.99]Would you welcome me?
[03:20.15]Try now to breathe
[03:26.26]Cry enough you are now with me
[03:32.36]And leave now answers bleed
[03:39.81]For my mistakes, I am to blame
[03:46.41]Made her believe that it was all metaphore
[03:53.49]I’d give my life to have you near once again
[03:59.84]Take me away
[04:02.63]Could you forgive me?
[04:13.73]Could you forgive...
