[id: cipbhnqn]
[ar:Epica]
[ti:The Obsessive Devotion]
[al:The Divine Conspiracy]
[by:BlackSun]

[00:00.00][00:50.03][01:01.74][01:21.89][01:32.92][01:42.68][02:09.62][02:29.44][02:40.76][03:00.00][03:14.97][03:36.22][04:23.72][04:46.16][05:29.89][05:49.70][06:05.28][06:14.51][06:21.12][06:28.93][06:32.82][06:35.39]
[00:40.14][00:50.72]Don’t you ever blind me
[00:42.91]Don’t be a foolish thief
[00:44.72][02:03.32]- Am I?
[00:45.66]Don’t you ever bring yourself to grief
[00:53.59]Don’t ever trick my mind
[00:55.38]- Did I?
[00:56.26]Don’t you think that you can lie to me
[01:00.70]- Did I lie?
[01:02.11][02:10.00][03:15.97]Fortuna exprimitur artibus falsis
[01:12.05][02:20.00][03:26.66]Et mendacem memorem esse oportet
[01:22.74][02:30.75]If he is your moon, I will be your earth
[01:27.68][02:35.63]To which you can return, safely or injured
[01:33.42][02:41.38]I feel only misery for myself when I
[01:38.67][02:46.69]Look through the eyes of someone else
[01:58.93]Don’t you choke and bind me
[02:01.63]Don’t be a bleeding heart
[02:04.19]Fold and walk away or play your cards
[02:08.69]- Let us play!
[02:50.69]I can't even recognize, the path which has to be
[02:56.00]Taken to enter infinity
[03:05.27]- Don't you dare me
[03:06.81]I dare you
[03:08.00]- You don't care about me
[03:09.83]I care about you
[03:10.75]- Don't you touch me
[03:13.19]- Liar
[04:18.61]Adoratio permanebit
[04:21.36]Quotiens me eges, adero
[04:24.04]I prefer to be unhappy with you
[04:29.29]Rather than being depressed without you
[04:34.66][05:20.64]I belong to someone, I'm dedicated to
[04:39.79]Nothing lasts forever, but you, you do...
[05:10.03]I prefer to be a liar just like you
[05:15.27]To fulfil my deepest desires
[05:25.96]But all that I desire is you
[05:34.39]One thoughtless moment passes in slow motion
[05:40.71]As I lie down I realise that...
[05:44.26]All I wish is to get rid of this Obsessive Devotion
[05:58.09][06:30.14]Venia ad vitam aeternam
[06:02.15]Non mihi, non tibi, sed nobis
[06:06.25]Hit me as you can
[06:10.06]Beat me as you wish
[06:13.68]Liar
[06:14.82]Fortuna mutua coniuncti
[06:18.19]Per tota saecula futura
[06:22.05]I effaced myself for you
[06:26.18]But now I regret
[06:33.14]This is the end

