[id: ascqwlsu]
[ar:Oomph!]
[ti:Sandman]
[al:True or Dare]
[by:lestat02]
[00:01.55]Sandman
[00:03.16]Oomph
[00:12.43][00:38.93][01:03.56][01:15.23][01:30.22][01:55.67][02:20.06][02:46.31][03:12.56][03:26.73]
[00:13.98][01:30.66]Europe, wake up!
[00:17.34]Can’t you see your children lined up?
[00:20.89]On the edge of the abyss they wait
[00:26.67]Europe, fucked up
[00:30.47]Scared to go to sleep, they stay up
[00:34.02]Prisoners of fate
[00:39.30][00:52.12][01:56.04][02:08.67]La Le Lu
[00:41.85][01:58.10]Someone’s got their eye on you
[00:45.09][02:01.70]Now the poorest kids are sleeping
[00:49.01][02:05.50]You should sleep too
[00:54.60][02:11.34]And the little hearts freeze through
[00:57.90][02:14.59]When the other kids are calling
[01:01.76][02:18.75]You’re worthless too
[01:04.13][01:17.17][02:20.68][02:33.62][03:15.23][03:28.65]Sandman, Sandman
[01:06.67][02:23.42][03:17.97]Please put out the lights
[01:10.60][02:26.90][03:21.39]The truth is a big scam
[01:12.96][02:29.45][03:24.06]So let me dream tonight
[01:19.96][02:36.22][03:31.57]Stand here by my side
[01:24.00][02:40.08][03:35.12]Sprinkle stardust into my eyes
[01:27.68][02:44.01][03:39.23]And let me sleep ’til I die
[01:34.15]Can’t you see your children hate us?
[01:37.88]Slowly, surely they are damned to fail
[01:43.35]Europe, pumped up
[01:46.84]Like a big casino gone bust
[01:50.44]Everyone’s “for sale”!
[02:47.12][03:00.06]"Let them eat cake!" someone said
[02:50.66]But all the children want is bread
[02:53.84]Screaming their lungs out every night
[02:56.82]The hunger burning deep inside!
[03:03.22]Until the day she lost her head
[03:06.77]Let me show you prosperity
[03:09.69]Where children long for what they need
