[id: lwvlawsh]
[ar:Ozzy Osbourne]
[ti:Diggin' Me Down]
[al:Scream]
[by:尊]
[00:00.00][03:30.15]歌手：Ozzy Osbourne
[00:02.00]专辑：Scream
[00:04.00]【Diggin' Me Down】
[00:06.00]歌词：尊
[00:08.00][01:54.87][02:03.40][02:11.92][02:22.85][02:44.88][03:37.38][03:48.13][04:10.57][04:32.50][05:19.77]
[01:47.07]You're saving the saved,
[01:48.87]Men and women enslaved,
[01:50.73]Propagating the messiah conception
[01:55.55]The rich getting richer,
[01:57.40]Paint you into the picture,
[01:59.51]Give the poor immaculate deception
[02:04.51]Where are you Father?
[02:06.36]Why don't you save us?
[02:08.65]The fallen are dying alone
[02:12.48]How can you shut off their cries?
[02:14.89]Ignore a new genocide?

[02:17.18][03:42.76]So come on, Jesus,
[02:19.28]We're all here waiting just for you
[02:26.44][03:52.03]How long must we keep on waiting?
[02:30.41]The faithful and blind are keepin' me, keepin' me down

[02:34.92][04:00.69]How long? 'Cause my faith is breaking,
[02:39.00][04:04.71]The pure and divine are diggin' me, diggin' me down
[03:12.47]Do you live in the light
[03:14.21]Or in the dead of the night?
[03:16.51]Sanctimonious promises broken

[03:21.13]Hypocritical sin,
[03:23.05]Dying slowly within,
[03:25.39]Is the sacred truth forever unspoken?

[03:31.82]Bohemian rapture,
[03:34.23]Beware the dark side of the Son.
[03:38.31]You're just a self-made messiah,
[03:40.47]Selling brimstone and fire

[03:45.04]Don't keep us waiting here for you
[03:56.05]The faithful and blind are bringin' me, bringin' me down

[04:11.56][Guitar Solo]
[04:44.88]How will I know you, Mr. Jesus Christ?
[04:52.78]Have you already been here once or twice?

[05:02.12]The son of man are obsolete façade,
[05:10.77]How will I know that you're the son of God?
[05:17.49]Yeah
