[id: vuivpnsv]
[ar:Ozzy Osbourne]
[ti:Let Me Hear You Scream]
[by:leoko]

[00:07.97][01:14.13][02:20.69][03:19.76]Let me hear you scream!
[00:10.24][01:22.64][02:25.01]
[00:17.05]I’m black and blue, beat up, but still I take the blows;
[00:24.42]‘Cause all I need is blood and sweat and skin and bones!

[00:31.80]I’ll take this rage,
[00:33.67]Rattle your cage,
[00:35.67]Nobody said it’s easy!
[00:39.36]It’s do or die,
[00:41.05]Only the strong survive!

[00:44.17]Get ready for the last stand!
[00:47.80]Get ready, I’m your hangman!

[00:52.17][01:58.64][02:43.06][02:57.83]Let me hear you scream like you want it! (Want it!)
[00:56.05][02:02.44][02:46.75][03:01.46]Let me hear you yell like you mean it! (Mean it!)
[00:59.67][02:06.13][02:50.38][03:05.20]If you’re gonna go down:
[01:01.92][02:08.00][02:52.33][03:06.95]Go loud!
[01:02.50][02:08.81][02:53.14][03:07.89]Go strong!
[01:03.38][02:09.81][02:54.08][03:08.82]Go proud!
[01:04.32][02:10.69][02:55.26][03:09.76]Go on!
[01:05.13][02:11.56][02:56.01][03:10.64]Go hard or go home!
[01:06.81][01:10.44][02:13.50][02:16.94][03:12.70][03:16.09]Let me hear you-
[01:09.00][01:12.25][02:15.25][02:18.75][03:14.08][03:18.02](Let me hear you-)
[01:17.44](scream, scream, scream, scream…)
[01:23.57]I’ll pull you up and push you right back in your place!
[01:30.89]I’ll take you down and wipe that smile right off your face!

[01:38.33]I’ll watch you break,
[01:40.26]Your mine to take,
[01:42.08]Don’t blink; you just might miss it!
[01:45.69]It’s all or nothing,
[01:47.82]Nowhere left to run!

[01:50.32]Are you ready for the last fight!?
[01:54.33]Get ready with the war cry!

[02:27.44][Guitar Solo]


