[id: lsclhvsc]
[ar:Ozzy Osbourne]
[ti:Miracle Man]
[al:No Rest for the Wicked]
[by:Klaus Schäfer]

[00:23.35][00:29.41]I'm looking for a Miracle Man
[00:26.54]That tells me no lies,
[00:32.79]Who's not in disguise
[00:35.79][00:49.29][00:58.98][01:16.10][01:32.79][01:45.10][02:47.35][03:05.78][03:32.22]
[00:37.79]I don't know where he'll come from
[00:40.42]And I don't know where he's been,
[00:43.60]But it's not our jimmy sinner
[00:47.60]Because he's so obscene
[00:52.79][01:33.72][01:37.29][01:39.79][03:06.59][03:11.41][03:13.97][03:17.16][03:20.41][03:23.59]Miracle Man got busted,
[00:55.29][03:27.16]Miracle Man got busted
[01:03.10]Today I saw a Miracle Man,
[01:05.60]On TV cryin'
[01:08.79]Such a hypocritical man,
[01:12.85]Born again, Dyin'
[01:18.04]He don't know where he's goin'
[01:20.48]But we sure know where he's been,
[01:24.04]It was our little Jimmy sinner
[01:27.47]Our eyes are on the screen
[01:42.66]Miracle Man
[02:33.28]A Devil with a crucifix,
[02:36.66]Brimstone and fire,
[02:40.03]He needs another carnal fix
[02:44.16]To take him higher and higher
[02:48.35]Now Jimmy he got busted
[02:51.72]With his pants down,
[02:55.34]Repent ye wretched sinners,
[02:59.03]Self righteous clown
