[id: pqwvovsu]
[ar:Illidiance]
[ti:Fading Away]
[al:Damage Theory]
[by:Skhrnykhsk]

[00:40.45][01:13.25][01:31.85][02:19.46][02:35.00][02:53.63][03:17.79][03:25.63][03:43.93][03:51.81][04:00.46]
[00:43.25]When I’ve opened my plastic eyelids I’ve stored you
[00:50.89]Virus of restricted emotion rapidly filled my nano brain
[00:59.36]I’m not able to rectify the error in a the program
[01:07.16]Failed to erase your image, segments of code forms your face again
[01:14.25][02:20.56][02:36.00][03:26.43]Kill me now, stop the synthetic heart
[01:20.02][02:25.91][02:41.99][03:31.82]No, I can’t do it by myself
[01:22.51][02:28.65][02:44.67][03:34.60]Time is running out and disappearing for us
[01:28.06][02:34.06][02:50.08][03:39.87]So it’s the time to fade away
[01:49.47]My own feelings are just a side-effect of the test
[01:57.22]Why it becomes so painful to realize that you’re just a tool?
[02:05.43]Life procreated me and now it dumps me as a waste,
[02:12.96]It kills my self-rendered nature, my cyber love violates their rules
[03:10.61][03:18.32]For my love there is are no asylum's left
[03:12.73][03:20.94]But I’m a leving human being
[03:14.61][03:22.56]There’s no place for my synthetic fate
[03:16.71][03:24.73]And I want to scream
[03:47.85][03:55.98]Now it’s the time to fade away
