[id: vwvpwnqu]
[ar:Iron Maiden]
[ti:The Legacy]
[00:18.22]Tell you a thing
[00:20.09]That you ought to know
[00:22.95]Two minutes of your time
[00:25.37]Then on you go

[00:27.92]Tell tale of the men
[00:30.22]All dressed in black
[00:32.65]That most of them
[00:35.14]Not coming back

[00:37.82]Sent off to the war
[00:40.43]To play little games
[00:42.91]And on their return
[00:45.28]Can't name no names

[00:47.89]Some strange yellow gas
[00:50.26]Has played with their minds
[00:52.81]Has reddened their eyes
[00:55.36]Removed all the lies

[00:57.84]And strange as it sounds
[01:00.39]Death knows no bounds
[01:02.88]How many get well
[01:05.31][01:25.15]Only time will tell

[03:21.10]You lie in your death bed now
[03:23.83]But what did you bring to the table
[03:26.63]Brought us only holy sin
[03:29.12]Utter trust is a deadly thing

[03:31.92]To the prayer of holy peace
[03:34.65]We didn't know what was lying underneath
[03:37.58]So how could we be such fools
[03:39.66]And to think that we thought you the answer

[03:43.64]I can't begin to understand in all the lies
[03:49.12]But on your death bed I can see it in you eyes
[03:54.90]Just as clear as all the sweat upon your brow
[03:59.94]It really makes sense I can see it clearly now

[04:04.12]Tangled up in a web of lies
[04:06.85]Could have been a way to prophesise
[04:09.72]Unaware of the consequence
[04:12.41]Not aware of the secrets that you kept

[04:15.02]Nothing that we could believe
[04:17.75]To reveal the façade of faceless men
[04:20.56]Not a thing that we could foresee
[04:23.17]Now a sign that would tell us the outcome

[04:26.96]You had us all strung out with
[04:29.57]promises of peace
[04:32.33]But all along you cover plan was to deceive
[04:37.86]Can it put to rights now only time will tell
[04:43.10]Your prophecies will send us all to hell as well

[04:47.30]Left to all our golden sons
[04:50.10]All to pick up on the peace
[04:52.58]You could have given all of them
[04:55.38]A little chance... at least

[04:58.00]Take the world to a better place
[05:00.75]Given them all just a little hope
[05:03.30]Just think what a legacy
[05:06.04]You now... will leave

[05:29.75]SOLO

[06:43.39]We seem destined to live in fear
[06:46.50]And some that would say Armageddon is near
[06:49.73]But where there's a life while there's hope
[06:52.66]That man won't self destruct

[06:56.58]Why can't we treat our fellow men
[06:59.07]With more respect and a shake of their hands
[07:02.98]But anger and loathing is rife
[07:05.68]The death on all sides is
[07:07.48]becoming a way of life

[07:09.97]We live in an uncertain world
[07:11.83]Fear understanding and ignorance
[07:14.57]is leading to death
[07:16.31]Only the corpses are left
[07:18.30]For vultures that prey on their bones

[07:34.26]But some are just not wanting peace
[07:36.56]Their whole life is death and misery
[07:40.80]The only thing that they know
[07:43.28]Fight fire with fire life is cheap

[07:47.08]But if they do stop to think
[07:49.19]That man is teetering right on the brink
[07:53.61]But do you think that they care
[07:55.91]They benefit from death and pain and despair


