[id: ivkbnwsu]
[ar:Within Temptation]
[ti:Faster]
[al:The Unforgiving]
[00:06.67]Artist: Within Temptation
[00:08.48]Album: The Unforgiving
[00:10.54]Title: Faster
[00:12.36]By: danricardo
[00:16.54][00:53.73][01:02.36][01:34.17][02:13.36][02:22.17][02:53.86][03:58.36]
[00:23.23]I can see, cause it’s burning deep inside.
[00:30.86]Like gasoline, a fire running wild.
[00:38.92]No more fear, cause I’m getting closer now.
[00:46.92]So unreal, but I like it anyhow.
[00:54.98][02:14.73]I go faster and faster and faster
[00:58.73][02:18.61]and faster and faster and faster and faster.
[01:02.86]I can’t live in a fairytale of lies.
[01:10.92][02:30.92][03:30.92]And I can’t hide from the feeling cause it’s right.
[01:18.92][02:38.86][03:38.92]And I go faster and faster and faster and faster for love.
[01:27.04][02:22.92][02:46.98][03:22.86][03:46.98]And I can’t live in a fairytale of lies.
[01:43.17]I can feel that you’ve mesmerized my heart.
[01:50.86]I feel so free.
[01:53.61]I’m alive, I’m breaking out.
[01:58.92]I won’t give in, cause I’m proud of all my scars
[02:06.80]And I can see I’ve been wasting too much time.
[03:54.67]A fairytale of lies.
